https://avac.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentWelcome to A-VAC’s new website. We added more Products and expanded Repair Services!                   Sign In     Create an Account
× 800-747-2821 Log In My Cart
Menu PRODUCTSVacuum PumpsHelium Leak DetectorsHelium Leak DetectorsAccessoriesRebuilt Vacuum PumpsExtraction EquipmentVacuum PumpsCold Traps/ Exhaust FiltersFittings / AccessoriesOvensVacuum Pump OilCapture Recovery PumpsChillersExtractorsShort Path DistillationRotovapsOvensCapture Recovery PumpsVacuum Pump OilHigh Performance Vacuum Pump OilFomblin/ Krytox OilsFyrquel FluidGreaseVacuum Tank SystemsSingle PumpDual PumpTurbo Pumped High Vacuum SystemsEco Turbo Pumping SystemClassic Turbo Pumping SystemPro Turbo Pumped Vacuum SystemVacuum Pump Repair KitsMajor KitsMinor KitsVacuum BlowersAtlas CopcoBOC Edwards StokesElmo ReitschleOerlikon Vacuum BlowersExhaust Filters/ Intake Filters/ Cold TrapsIntakeExhaustCold TrapsNew Vacuum Pumps & OvensVacuum Chambers & SystemsGauges and TubesHigh Vacuum Gauges ATM TO-12 torrFittings, Hose and PartsFittingsHoseConnection KitsVacuum ValvesSERVICES & REPAIRVacuum Pump Repair Service OverviewVacuum Gauge and Leak Standard CalibrationsHelium Leak TestingHelium Leak Detector RepairsREFURBISHED PUMPS SALE STOCKNEW ON SALE PUMPSABOUT A-VACAPPLICATIONSBRANDSINFO CENTERQ&A’sDOCUMENTATIONCONTACTBLOG PRIVACY POLICY Privacy Policy & NoticeEffective Date: 1/1/2000This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.avac.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:What information we collectWith whom it is sharedHow it can be correctedHow it is securedHow policy changes will be communicatedHow to address concerns over misuse of personal dataInformation Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:See what data we have about you, if anyChange/correct any data we have about youHave us delete any data we have about youExpress any concern you have about our use of your dataSecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-747-2821 or via email pumpexperts@avac.com.RegistrationIn order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.OrdersWe request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.Surveys & ContestsFrom time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.A-VAC Industries, Inc. Is Proud To Be A Veteran Owned Business Since 1969Member of American Vacuum Society (AVS), Society of Vacuum Coaters (SVC). Association of Vacuum Equipment Manufacturers (AVEM) Recent Blog Posts What Happens to Sound in a Vacuum? October 2, 2020 Vacuum Pump Facts: True or False? September 29, 2020 5 Tips for Purchasing a Leak Detector September 4, 2020HOMEPRODUCTSVACUUM SERVICE & REPAIREDWARDS VACUUM PUMP REPAIRABOUT A-VACINDUSTRY APPLICATIONSBRANDSDOCUMENTATIONQ & A’sCONTACT USBLOGCAPABILITY STATEMENTTERMS & CONDITIONSRETURN AND REFUND POLICYPRIVACY POLICYA-VAC Industries Headquarters 1845 S. Lewis St. , Anaheim, CA 92805Toll Free Phone: 800-747-2821 Local Phone: 714-938-1300 FAX: 714-938-0899 Email: pumpexperts@avac.comPick up and delivery hours: 7:00am-3:30pm PST Monday – Friday
Do NOT follow this link or you will be banned from the site!Schedule a Repair With Our Vacuum Pump Repair SpecialistName *FirstLastBusiness / Organization *Email *Phone *Request *PhoneSubmit
×
